(Amy:)He showed up in the middle of the night
with his bongos.
l foolishly thought
it was some sort of musical booty call.
(Leonard:)Poor guy.
He must have been exhausted.
(Leonard:)Sheldon like to sleep
While Leonard play the bongo
- That was kind of uncalled for.
- No, it was called for.
(Sheldon:)What's going on?
(Penny:)Sheldon, this craziness has gone
on long enough.
(Penny:)Please come home
so I can cut your hair.
(Sheldon:)Penny, you're not trained.
You're not licensed.
And most importantly, you don't have
access to my haircut records.
(Penny:)All right, honey, look...
(Penny:)...we've known each other
for a long time now, right?
l've taken you to Disneyland,
l kicked a bully in the nuts for you.
l sing you "Soft Kitty" when you're sick,
you've even seen me naked once.
I'm sorry, what?